{
    "id": "8a40125af15848578b8fc410a93ddbbf",
    "title": "Adjective Or Adverb",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Please write more …………………………",
            "description": "Here the adverb legibly modifies the verb write. ",
            "answers": [
                "legible",
                "legibly"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "How is your grandmother? Is she any …………………………..?",
            "description": "Use the comparative form when there is an idea of change. ",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "better",
                "best"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He can speak …………………………… German.",
            "description": "Here the adjective fluent modifies the noun German.",
            "answers": [
                "fluent",
                "fluently"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The small house was …………………………… bigger than a hut.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hard",
                "hardly"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She works the ………………………. when she does something for her family.",
            "description": "Use the superlative form after the.",
            "answers": [
                "hard",
                "harder",
                "hardest"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "A car cannot carry as ………………………… people as a bus.",
            "description": "Use the positive form of the adjective in the expression as...as... Use many with plural nouns and much with uncountable nouns. ",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much",
                "more"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "That was a …………………………… thing to do.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "stupid",
                "stupider",
                "stupidest"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………….. watch action movies.",
            "description": "Either rarely or seldom is possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "rarely",
                "rare",
                "seldom"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "They waited ……………………………. for their father.",
            "description": "Here the adverb anxiously modifies the verb waited. ",
            "answers": [
                "anxious",
                "anxiously"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "All of a …………………………., a dark figure emerged in the hallway.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sudden",
                "suddenly"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He ran as ………………………… as he could.",
            "description": "Fast can be an adjective and an adverb. The positive form is used in the expression as...as...",
            "answers": [
                "fast",
                "fastly",
                "faster"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She looked …………………………",
            "description": "Look is a copular verb. We use adjectives, not adverbs to modify copular verbs. ",
            "answers": [
                "sad",
                "sadly"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}